giveforward.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to the GiveForward website (the “Site”), which is designed, owned and operated by GiveForward, a Delaware corporation (“GiveForward”) to provide visitors with online fundraising pages, related features and services. All references to (“we” “us”, “our” or “the Company”) refer to GiveForward.  We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy.  The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Company Site.  This privacy policy applies only to information collected by or through the Site.  It does not apply to information obtained by other means.  By visiting this website, you consent to these practices.  Please take a moment to review the sections below.

**What Information do we Collect?**

We may collect both personally identifiable information about you and non-personally identifiable information about your visit when you access our website.

_Personally Identifiable Information_ :  The personally identifiable information we collect includes information you submit to us.  For example, if you subscribe to online services we offer or register for certain services with us online that require registration, agree to participate in on-line surveys, participate in on-line contests, sweepstakes and promotions sponsored by us, make certain on-line information requests to us, or want to establish a profile for submission of user generated content available to other Site visitors, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information such as your contact information (e.g., name, phone number, address and e-mail address) and user demographic information (e.g., gender, age, hobbies or interests).  Because participation in these activities is completely voluntary, you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

_Non-personally Identifiable Information_ :

The non-personally identifiable information we collect includes the domain name of the site providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, which is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university.  Our service may also collect your browser type and version, the operating system your computer is running, and other site visit data such as the pages you view, the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine), information you search for, information or ads you click on, the average time spent on our website, and the web site you visit after this web site.  Much of this information is tracked through log files, which are stored on Company’s servers.  **As explained below, we may link this information with your personal information when we feel that it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules and policies or terms of service or to protect our Sites, customers or others.**

**How is Your Information Used?**

_Personally Identifiable Information_ :  GiveForward considers the personally identifiable information contained in our business records to be confidential.  We will not sell, rent, or share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties [ ] without your consent, except as described in this policy.  We use your personally identifiable information such as your Contact information to send you confirmation notices regarding services you have requested and to notify contest or sweepstakes winners and award prizes..

_Non-personally Identifiable Information_ :  Non-personal information collected about your site visits, anonymous survey information, and certain aggregated demographic information will be used for purposes of reporting survey results and to allow us to better understand the entire audience that is visiting our site.  Except as noted below we track and record IP addresses that access our site for reporting and profiling purposes only.  We monitor and analyze this information to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our site and better tailor the site to our visitors’ needs.  We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, gather broad demographic information, and administer our website.

_Sharing with Service Providers_ :  To do all of the things described above, we may share your personally identifiable information with our business partners or others who work for us such as service providers, vendors, contractors and agents (collectively “Service Providers”).  We provide our Service Providers with the information they require to perform services for us, but we ask our Service Providers not to use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

_Other disclosures of Personally Identifiable and Non-personally Identifiable Information_ :  To the extent permitted by law, any information collected over our website or concerning its use (personal and non-personal) may be disclosed to government authorities or third parties pursuant to a legal request, subpoena, or other process that requires disclosure of information or other process that requires disclosure of information.  We may also use or disclose your information to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use and as permitted by law to collect debts, fight fraud or protect the rights or property of Company, our customers, our website, its users, or third parties, or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. **We may also link non-personally identifiable information such as your IP address and other information with your personal information when we feel that it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules and policies or terms of service or to protect our Sites, customers or others.**

_Information Posted to Public Forums:_ This site at some or all times makes forums, public commenting and/or message boards, available to its users.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  Company cannot accept any responsibility for ensuring the privacy of information that you choose to disclose in these areas.

_Supplemental Information from Third Parties:_ This site may supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For example, when connecting through Facebook Connect. This information may be received from our partners in sponsored content sections or from other third parties.  The type of information that is shared with us could include user contact information (like name and email address) and user demographic information (like zip code, age or income level).  This Site will use supplemental information received from third parties in accordance with this privacy policy.  However, when you leave the Company website to go to another site, the privacy statement of the other site will apply to the use of your personal information.

**What About Cookies?**

A cookie is a piece of information that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive.  A cookie allows Company to determine that a visit has occurred within our site, as well as which pages were viewed.  Cookies are not used to identify you and will not collect personal information.  You can decide if and how your computer will accept cookies by configuring your preferences option within your web browser.  If you choose to decline cookies, however, some of the functionality of the Site may be impaired.

**What Information is Collected from Children?**

GiveForward is concerned about children’s privacy.  This website is not directed at children under the age of 13.  It is a general audience site with content directed primarily at individuals 13 and over.  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent and unless expressly identified on specific pages of our website.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever.  If a child does provide us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us by sending an e-mail to info@giveforward.com or calling us at (312) 957-6113,

Upon notification, we will delete from our records any information collected from children under the age of 13.

**How Do We Protect Personally Identifiable Information Collected on this Site?**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information in our possession from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.  However, Company does not warrant or represent that its level of security meets or exceeds any particular standard.  You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free.

**What if I am a Non-U.S. User?**

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using this web site, you consent to this transfer. You also consent to the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with this website in the federal and state courts of, and in accordance with the laws of, the state of Deleware.

**What Happens to Your Information if There is a Corporate Change of Control?**

In the event of a corporate change in control resulting from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, GiveForward reserves the right to transfer your personal information to the new party in control.

**What About Changes to This Privacy Policy?**

Company reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.  We will notify you of material changes to this privacy policy by posting the revised policy with the date it was revised on this page.  Your continued use of our websites constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.  We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect.

**How Can You Ask Questions or Raise Concerns?**

If you have other questions or concerns about our privacy policies or data use, or wish to change your options, please-mail us at info@giveforward.com

Effective: January 2011
